19th-20th Century North American Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 15)
    - Libraries (Box 102)
      - Public Library (Box 102)
        - Plans & sections (Box 102)
        - Exterior (Box 102)
        - Interior (Box 102)
      - Monuments (Box 102)
        - Grant's Tomb (Box 102)
        - Hudson-Fulton Monument (Box 102)
        - Soldiers & Sailors Monument (Box 102)
      - Museums (Box 102)
        - Academic of Design (Box 102)
        - Frick Collection (Box 102)
        - Guggenheim Museum (Box 103)
        - Heyden Planetarium (Box 103)
        - Heyden Planetarium (Box 103)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 103)
          - Cloister (Box 103)
        - Museum of Modern Art (Box 103)
          - Plans & Sections (Box 103)
          - Exterior (Box 103)
          - Interior (Box 103)
        - Natural Historical Museum (Box 103)
        - Roerich Museum (Box 103)
        - Whitney Museum (Box 103)
      - Office Buildings (Box 103)
        - Various (Box 103)
        - American Radiator Building (Box 104)
        - Barkeley-Vesey Telephone Building (Box 104)
        - Bayard Building (Box 104)
        - Bayard Building (Box 104)
        - Bogardus Building (Box 104)
        - British Overseas Airlines Building (Box 104)
        - Bush Building, 1917 (Box 104)
        - Chanin Building (Box 104)
        - Chrysler Building (Box 104)
        - Cunard Building (Box 104)
        - Delmonico Building (Box 104)
        - Delmonico Building (Box 104)
        - Empire State Building (Box 104)
        - Fiske Rubber Co. Building (Box 104)
        - Flatiron (Fuller) Building (Box 104)
        - Flatiron (Fuller) Building (Box 104)
        - General Motors Co. Building (Box 104)
        - Ghorham Building (Box 104)
        - Harper & Bros. Building (Box 104)
        - Harper & Bros. Building (Box 104)
        - Herald Building (Box 104)
        - Lever House (Box 104)
        - Liggett Building (Box 105)
        - McGraw-Hill Building (Box 105)
        - Metropolitan Life Insurance (Box 105)
        - New York Daily News Building (Box 105)
        - Owings-Corning Fiberglass Building (Box 105)
        - Pan Am Building (Box 105)
        - Panama National Tourist Commissions (Box 105)
        - Paramount Building (Box 105)
        - Park Row Building (Box 105)
        - Rockefeller Center (Box 105)
          - Plans (Box 105)
          - Exterior (Box 105)
          - Interior (Box 105)
        - Radio City Hall (Box 105)
          - Lighting (Box 105)
        - Royal Dutch Airlines Offices (Box 105)
        - Seagram Building (Box 105)
        - Singer Building (Box 105)
        - Standard Oil Co. Building (Box 105)
        - Telephone & Telegraph Building (Box 105)
        - Times Building (Box 106)
        - Tower Building (Box 106)
        - Tribune Building (Box 106)
        - Western Union Building (Box 106)
        - Whitehall Building (Box 106)
        - Woolworth Building (Box 106)
        - World Trade Center (Box 106)
        - World Building (Box 106)
      - Parks (Box 106)
        - Various (Box 106)
        - Astoria Park (Box 106)
        - Bryant Park (Box 106)
        - Central Park (Box 106)
        - Jacob Riis Park (Box 106)
      - Prisons (Box 106)
      - Reservoirs (Box 106)
        - Central Park Reservoir- Proposed Fountain (Box 106)
          Xx General views- looking S. across 42nd St. 1855
        - Croton Reservoir (Box 106)
      - Restaurants (Box 106)
      - Schools (Box 106)
        - Columbia University (Box 106)
        - Hunter College (Box 106)
        - New School of Social Research (Box 106)
        - New York University (Box 106)
      - Squares (Box 106)
      - Stations (Box 106)
        - Various (Box 106)
        - Old Grand Central (Box 107)
        - Grand Central Station (Box 107)
          - Plans, Section & Designs (Box 107)
          - Exterior (Box 107)
          - Interior (Box 107)
        - Pennsylvania Station (Box 107)
          - Plans (Box 107)
          - Exterior (Box 107)
          - Interior (Box 107)
        - Third Avenue Car Barns (Box 107)
      - Stores (Box 107)
        - General (Box 107)
        - America House (Box 107)
        - Appleton (Box 107)
        - Artek-Pascoe (Box 107)
        - Ciro (Box 107)
        - Corning Glass Co. (Box 107)
        - Delicatessen Shop (Box 107)
        - Durand-Rull Shop (Box 107)
        - Edison Shop (Box 107)
        - Gorham Shop (Box 107)
        - Grover & Baker (Box 107)
        - Hardman, Peck & Co. Shop (Box 108)
        - Lederen de Paris (Box 108)
        - Lillian Park Ave. Inc. (Box 108)
        - Lord &Taylor (Box 108)
        - Macy's (Box 108)
        - Maillard's (Box 108)
        - Phyfe's (Box 108)
        - Rebajes (Box 108)
        - Spear's (Box 108)
        - Tourneur (Box 108)
        - Tradewinds (Box 108)
        - Wanamaker (Box 108)
        - Wyle, Henny (Box 108)
      - Taverns, Inns, Etc (Box 108)
        - Fraunce's Tavern (Box 108)
      - Theaters (Box 108)
        - Various (Box 108)
        - Globe Theater (Box 108)
        - Lincoln Center (Box 108)
        - Madison Square Garden (Box 108)
        - New Theater (Box 108)
          - Plans, sections, models, etc. (Box 108)
          - Exterior (Box 108)
          - Interior (Box 108–109)
        - Pike's Opera House (Box 109)
        - Ziegfield Theater (Box 109)
      - Zoos (Box 109)
    - Nordhoff, NJ (Box 109)
    - Norfolk, VA (Box 109)
    - Norman, OK (Box 109)
    - Norris, TN (Box 109)
    - Norristown, PA (Box 109)
    - North Branford, CT (Box 109)
    - North Dartmouth, MA (Box 109)
    - North Easton, MA (Box 109)
      - Various (Box 109)
      - Houses (Box 109)
      - Libraries (Box 109)
    - Northford, CT (Box 110)
    - Northampton, MA (Box 110)
    - North Guilford, CT (Box 110)
    - North Haven, CT (Box 110)
    - North Hollywood, CA (Box 110)
      - Houses (Box 110)
        - Barsha House (Box 110)
        - Roth House (Box 110)
    - North Kingston, RI (Box 110)
    - North Plain, CT (Box 110)
    - Norton, MA (Box 110)
      - Schools (Box 110)
        - Wheaton College (Box 110)
    - Norwalk, CT (Box 110)
    - Norwich, CT (Box 110)
    - Nottingham, PA (Box 110)
    - Nyack, NY (Box 110)
    - Oak Bluff, MA (Martha's Vineyard) (Box 110)
    - Oak Park, IL (Box 110)
      - Various (Box 110)
      - Churches (Box 110)
        - Unity Temple (Box 110)
      - Houses (Box 110)
        - Various (Box 110)
        - Heurtley House (Box 110)
        - Martin House (Box 111)
        - Thomas House (Box 111)
        - F.L. Wright House (Box 111)
        - F.L. Wright Studio (Box 111)
    - Oak Ridge, TN (Box 111)
    - Oberlin, OH (Box 111)
    - Ocean Grove, NJ (Box 111)
    - Oceanside, CA (Box 111)
    - Ocean Springs, MO (Box 111)
    - Odessa, DE (Box 111)
    - Ogdensburg, CA (Box 111)
    - Ogden, UT (Box 111)
    - Ojai, CA (Box 111)
      - Houses (Box 111)
        - Various (Box 111)
        - C.H. Wyle House (Box 111)
    - Okemos, MI (Box 111)
    - Oklahoma City, OK (Box 111)
    - Old Lyme, CT (Box 111)
    - Old Westbury, NY (Box 111)
      - Houses (Box 111)
        - Goodyear House (Box 111)
    - Oley Toenship, PA (Box 112)
    - Oneida, NY (Box 112)
    - Opelousas, LA (Box 112)
    - Orange, CT (Box 112)
      - Miller (Box 112)
    - Orange, NJ (Box 112)
    - Orinda, CA (Box 112)
    - Orwell, VT (Box 112)
    - Ossining, NY (Box 112)
    - Overbrook, PA (Box 112)
    - Owatonna, MI (Box 112)
    - Oyster Bay, Lon Island, NY (Box 112)
    - Palatine Bridge, NY (Box 112)
    - Pacific Grove, CA (Box 112)
    - Pacific Grove, CA (Box 112)
    - Palmer, MA (Box 112)
    - Palm Springs, CA (Box 112)
      - Miller House, Neutra Architect (Box 112)
    - Palmyra, NY (Box 112)
    - Palo Alto, CA (Box 112)
      - Houses (Box 112)
        - Various (Box 112)
        - Hanna House (Box 112)
      - Schools (Box 112)
    - Palo Colorado Canyon, CA (Box 112)
    - Paradise Valley, AZ (Box 112)
    - Park Forest, IL (Box 112)
    - Park Ridge, IL (Box 112)
    - Parris Island, SC (Box 113)
    - Pasadena, CA (Box 113)
      - Various (Box 113)
      - Houses (Box 113)
        - Blacker House (Box 113)
        - Coppell House (Box 113)
        - Francis House (Box 113)
        - Gamble House (Box 113)
        - Huntington House (Box 113)
        - Millard House (Box 113)
        - Reeve House (Box 113)
        - Richter House (Box 113)
        - S. Francis Court (Box 113)
      - Schools (Box 113)
    - Paterson, NJ (Box 113)
    - Peabody, MA (Box 113)
      - Houses (Box 113)
        - Various (Box 113)
        - Derby House (Box 113)
        - Oak Hill (Box 113)
    - Peekskill, NY (Box 113)
    - Pelham Bay, NY (Box 113)
    - Pelham Manor, NY (Box 113)
    - Pensacola, FL (Box 113)
    - Peterburg, VA (Box 113)
    - Philadelphia, PA (Box 113)
      - General (Box 113)
        - Air views (Box 113)
      - Plans & Maps (Box 113)
        - Various (Box 113)
        - By William PENN (Box 114)
      - Planning (Box 114)
        - 1960 Plan (Box 114)
      - Banks (Box 114)
        - Various (Box 114)
        - Bank of PENN (Box 114)
        - Branch Bank of the U.S. (Box 114)
        - Guarantee Trust (Box 114)
        - Merchant's Exchange (Box 114)
        - Philadelphia Savings Foundation Society (Box 114)
        - Provident Life & Trust Co. (Box 114)
      - Bridges (Box 114)
      - Churches (Box 114)
        - Various (Box 114)
        - Christ Church (Box 114)
        - First Baptist (Box 114)
        - First Presbyterian (Box 114)
        - Old Swedes Church (Box 114)
        - S. Peter's (Box 114)
      - Clubs (Box 114)
      - Expositions (Box 114)
        - Centennial Exhibition 1876 (Box 114)
          - Agriculture Hall (Box 115)
          - Art Gallery (Box 115)
          - British Executive Staff quarters (Box 115)
          - Horticulture Hall (Box 115)
          - Machinery Hall (Box 115)
          - Main Pavilion (Box 115)
          - Memorial Hall (Box 115)
      - Government Buildings (Box 115)
        - Various (Box 115)
        - City Hall (Box 115)
        - Independence Hall (Box 115)
        - Schuylkill Waterworks (Box 115)
      - Hospitals (Box 115)
        - Pennsylvania Hospital (Box 115)
        - Presbyterian Hospital (Box 115)
        - U.S. Naval Home (Box 115)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 115)
        - Various (Box 115–116)
        - Chew Mansion "Cliveden" (Box 116)
        - Johnson House (Box 116)
        - Livingstone House (Box 116)
        - Mellor House (Stables) (Box 116)
        - Morris House (Box 116)
        - Mount Pleasant (Box 116)
        - William Penn House (Box 116)
        - Powel House (Box 116)
        - Randolf House (Box 116)
        - Reed House (Box 116)
        - Reynolds-Morris House (Box 116)
        - Roberts House (Box 116)
        - Sedgley House (Box 116)
        - Slate House (Box 116)
        - Stenton House (Box 116)
        - Upsala Road House (Box 116)
        - Widener House (Box 116)
        - Woodlands House (Box 116)
        - Wyck House (Box 116)
      - Housing (Box 116)
        - Carl Mackley Houses (Box 116)
        - Guild House (Box 116)
        - Mill Creek Public Housing (Box 117)
        - Society Hill (Box 117)
      - Libraries (Box 117)
      - Museums (Box 117)
        - American Swedish Historical Institute (Box 117)
        - Athenaeum (Box 117)
        - Penn. Academy (Box 117)
        - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Box 117)
      - Office Buildings (Box 117)
        - Various (Box 117)
        - Penn. Center (Box 117)
        - PA Fire Insurance Co. (Box 117)
      - Prisons (Box 117)
        - Eastern Penitentiary (Box 117)
        - Moyamensing Pleasant (Box 117)
      - Restaurants (Box 117)
        - Grand's Restaurant (Box 117)
      - Schools (Box 117)
        - Various (Box 117)
        - Girard College (Box 117)
          - Competition 1832 (Box 117)
        - Oak Lane Country Day School (Box 118)
        - Philadelphia Academy of Natural (Box 118)
          - Various (Box 118)
          - Richards Medical & Biology Research Lab. By L. Kahnn (Box 118)
      - Stations (Box 118)
        - Broad St. Station (Box 118)
        - Southern and Western Station (Box 118)
        - Germantown & Norristown Station (Box 118)
        - Philadelphia & Reading Station (Box 118)
      - Stores (Box 118)
        - Wanamaker's (Box 118)
      - Theaters (Box 118)
    - Phillips Beach, MA (Box 118)
    - Phoenix, AZ (Box 118)
      - Hotels (Box 118)
      - Houses (Box 118)
        - Pauson House (Box 118)
        - "45 Degree Plan" House (Box 118)
        - Taliesin House (Box 118)
          - Exterior (Box 118)
          - Interior (Box 118)
    - Piedemont, CA (Box 119)
    - Pittsburgh, PA (Box 119)
      - Various (Box 119)
      - Churches (Box 119)
      - Government Buildings (Box 119)
        - Various (Box 119)
        - Allegheny County Court House (Box 119)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 119)
        - Frank House (Box 119)
      - Libraries (Box 119)
      - Office Buildings (Box 119)
      - Railroad Station (Box 119)
    - Pittsfield, MA (Box 119)
    - Pittston, PA (Box 119)
    - Plainfield, CT (Box 119)
    - Plainfield, IA (Box 119)
    - Plainville, CT (Box 119)
    - Plano, IL (Box 119)
    - Plattsburg, NY (Box 119)
    - Pleasantville, NY (Box 119)
    - Plymouth, CT (Box 119)
    - Plymouth, MA (Box 119)
    - Plymouth, MI (Box 119)
    - Pocahontas, IA (Box 119)
    - Poland Springs, ME (Box 119)
    - Port Chester, NY (Box 120)
      - Houses (Box 120)
    - Portland, CT (Box 120)
    - Portland, ME (Box 120)
      - Government Buildings (Box 120)
      - Houses (Box 120)
        - Various (Box 120)
        - Davis House (Box 120)
        - Stevens House (Box 120)
        - Victoria Mansion (Box 120)
    - Portland, OR (Box 120)
      - General (Box 120)
      - Cemeteries (Box 120)
      - Churches (Box 120)
        - Central Lutheran (Box 120)
        - St. Thomas More Chapel (Box 120)
        - Zion Lutheran (Box 120)
      - Clubs (Box 120)
      - Houses (Box 120)
        - Belluschi House (Box 120)
        - Moore House (Box 120)
        - Payne House (Box 120)
        - Yeon House (Box 121)
      - Office Buildings (Box 121)
      - Warehouses (Box 121)
    - Portsmouth, NH (Box 121)
      - Churches (Box 121)
      - Government Buildings (Box 121)
      - Houses (Box 121)
        - Various (Box 121)
        - Aldrich House (Box 121)
        - Boardman House (Box 121)
        - Buckminster House (Box 121)
        - Jaffrey House (Box 121)
        - Langdon House (Box 121)
        - McPhedris House (Warner) (Box 121)
        - Moffatt, Ladd House (Box 121)
        - Pierce Mansion (Box 121)
        - Wendell House (Box 121)
        - Wentworth-Gardner House (Box 121)
      - Libraries (Box 121)
      - Museums (Box 121)
    - Portsmouth, RI (Box 121)
    - Poughkeepsie, NY (Box 121)
    - Preston, CT (Box 121)
    - Princeton, NJ (Box 121)
      - Houses (Box 121)
      - Schools (Box 121)
        - Princeton University (Box 121)
          - Various (Box 121–122)
          - Alexander Hall (Box 122)
          - Blair Hall (Box 122)
          - Chancellor Green Library (Box 122)
          - Firestone Library (Box 122)
          - Graduate College (Box 122)
          - Gymnasium (Box 122)
          - Holder Hall (Box 122)
          - Little Stafford Hall (Box 122)
          - Marquand Chapel (Box 122)
          - Nassau Hall (Box 122)
          - Old Chapel (Box 122)
    - Prospect Park, PA (Box 122)
    - Providence, RI (Box 122)
      - General (Box 122)
      - Churches (Box 122)
        - Various (Box 122)
        - First Baptist Church (Box 122)
        - Congregational Church (Box 123)
      - Government Building (Box 123)
        - City Hall (Box 123)
        - State Capitol (Box 123)
      - Houses (Box 123)
        - Various (Box 123)
        - Ashton House (Box 123)
        - Beckwith House (Box 123)
        - Tully Bowen House (Box 123)
        - John Brown House (Box 123)
        - Joseph Brown House, 1774 (Box 123)
        - Carrington House (Box 123)
        - Cooke House (Box 123)
        - Dexter House (Box 123)
        - Dodge House (Box 123)
        - Foster House (Box 123)
        - Stephen Hopkins House (Box 123)
        - Hoppin House (Box 123)
        - Ives House (Box 123)
        - Mowry House (Box 123)
        - Nightingale House (Box 123)
        - Pendleton House (Box 123)
        - Watson House (Box 123)
      - Libraries (Box 123)
      - Museums (Box 123)
      - Stations (Box 123)
      - Schools (Box 123)
        - Brown University (Box 123–124)
        - Rhode Island School of Design (Box 124)
      - Stores (Box 124)
    - Pullman, IL (Box 124)
    - Quincy, MA (Box 124)
      - Churches (Box 124)
      - Houses (Box 124)
    - Racine, WI (Box 124)
      - Various (Box 124)
      - Houses (Box 124)
        - Hardy House (Box 124)
        - Johnson Cottage (Box 124)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 124)
        - Johnson Wax Co. (Box 124)
          - Various (Box 124)
          - Exterior (Box 124)
          - Interior (Box 124)
          - Research Towers (Box 124)
    - Radburn, NJ (Box 124)
    - Radnor, PA (Box 124)
    - Rahway, NJ (Box 124)
    - Raleigh, NC (Box 124)
      - Various (Box 124)
      - Government Buildings (Box 125)
      - Hospitals (Box 125)
    - Ranchos de Taos, NM (Box 125)
    - Randolph, NY (Box 125)
    - Reading, PA (Box 125)
    - Redding, CT (Box 125)
    - Red Hook, NY (Box 125)
    - Red Wing, MN (Box 125)
    - Redwood City, CA (Box 125)
    - Relay, MD (Box 125)
    - Rensselaer, NY (Box 125)
    - Rhinebeck, NY (Box 125)
    - Richfield Springs, NY (Box 125)
    - Richland Center, WI (Box 125)
    - Richmond, VA (Box 125)
      - Various (Box 125)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 125)
      - Churches (Box 125)
      - Government Buildings (Box 125)
        - City Hall (Box 125)
        - State Capitol (Box 125–126)
      - Hotels (Box 126)
      - Houses (Box 126)
        - Various (Box 126)
        - Wickham-Valentine House (Box 126)
    - Ridgefield, CT (Box 126)
    - River Forest, IL (Box 126)
      - Clubs (Box 126)
        - Golf Club (Box 126)
        - Women's Club (Box 126)
      - Houses (Box 126)
        - Drummond House (Box 126)
        - Roberts House (Box 126)
        - Walter House (Box 126)
    - Riverside, CA (Box 126)
      - Mission Inn (Box 126)
    - Riverside, IL (Box 126)
      - Various (Box 126)
      - Houses (Box 126)
        - Babson House (Box 126)
        - Coonley House (Box 126)
      - Schools (Box 126)
    - Rochester, MN (Box 126)
    - Rochester, NY (Box 126)
    - Rockingham, VT (Box 126)
    - Rockport, ME (Box 126)
    - Rockville, CT (Box 126–127)
    - Rocky Hill, CT (Box 127)
    - Roselle,IL (Box 127)
      - Schweiker House (Box 127)
    - Roslyn, NY (Box 127)
    - Ross, CA (Box 127)
      - Various (Box 127)
      - Beaver House (Box 127)
      - Dettner House (Box 127)
    - Roxbury, MA (Box 127)
    - Rye, MA (Box 127)
    - Sadadahoc, ME (Box 127)
    - Sag Harbor, L.I., NY (Box 127)
    - St. Albans, VT (Box 127)
    - St. Augustine, FL (Box 127)
      - Churches (Box 127)
        - Cathedral (Box 127)
        - Flayer Memorial Church (Box 127)
      - Hotels (Box 127)
    - S. Francis, LA (Box 127)
    - St. Genevieve, MO (Box 127)
    - St. Louis, MO (Box 127)
      - General (Box 127)
      - Airports (Box 127)
      - Bridges (Box 128)
      - Churches (Box 128)
        - Various (Box 128)
        - Church of the Messiah (Box 128)
        - S. Ann's (Box 128)
        - S. Mark's Church (Box 128)
        - Union Methodist Church (Box 128)
      - Exhibitions (Box 128)
        - Louisiana Purchase Exposition (Box 128)
      - Government Buildings (Box 128)
      - Hotels (Box 128)
      - Houses (Box 128)
        - Campbell House (Box 128)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 128)
        - Sample Machine Shop (Box 128)
      - Office Buildings (Box 128)
        - Various (Box 128)
        - American Stove, Co. (Box 128)
        - Bell Telephone Building (Box 128)
        - Chamber of Commerce Building (Box 128)
        - Union Trust Building (Box 128)
        - Wainwright Building (Box 129)
      - Schools (Box 129)
      - Stations (Box 129)
      - Stores (Box 129)
      - Tombs (Box 129)
    - St. Mathew's, KY (Box 129)
    - St. Paul, MN (Box 129)
      - Expositions (Box 129)
      - Government Buildings (Box 129)
        - Various (Box 129)
        - City Hall (Box 129)
    - Salem, MA (Box 129)
      - General (Box 129)
      - Banks (Box 129)
      - Churches (Box 129)
      - Government Buildings (Box 129)
        - Custom House (Box 129)
        - Hamilton Hall (Box 129)
        - Market House (Box 129)
      - Houses (Box 129)
        - Various (Box 129)
        - Assambly House (Box 129)
        - Boardman House (Box 129)
        - Cook House (Box 129)
        - Corwin House (Box 129)
          Xx the "Witch House"
        - Derby House (Box 129–130)
        - Downing House (Box 130)
        - English House (Box 130)
        - Enoch Dow House (Box 130)
        - Gardner Pingreeh (Box 130)
          - Exterior (Box 130)
          - Interior (Box 130)
        - Grimshaw House (Box 130)
        - Hunt House (Box 130)
        - Kimball House (Box 130)
        - Laurel Garles (Box 130)
        - McIntyre House (Box 130)
        - Pickering House (Box 130)
        - Pickman House (Box 130)
        - Pierce Nichols House (Box 130)
        - Ropes Mansion (Box 130)
        - Turner House (Box 130)
        - John Ward House (Box 130)
        - Ward-Cronin-Shield House (Box 130)
        - Witch House (Box 130)
      - Office Buildings (Box 130)
        - Archer Building (Box 130)
        - Stearns Building (Box 130)
      - Pioneer Village (Box 130)
      - Schools (Box 130)
      - Stations (Box 130)
      - Theaters (Box 130)
    - Salem, NJ (Box 130)
      - Houses (Box 130)
    - Salem, OR (Box 130)
      - Banks (Box 130)
      - Government Buildings (Box 130)
    - Salisbury, NC (Box 130)
    - Salt Lake City, UT (Box 130–131)
    - Sampson, NY (Box 131)
    - San Antonio, TX (Box 131)
      - Various (Box 131)
      - S. Jose de Aguayo (Box 131)
    - San Carlo, CA (Box 131)
    - San Diego, CA (Box 131)
      - Various (Box 131)
      - Salk Institute (Box 131)
      - Government Buildings (Box 131)
      - Churches (Box 131)
      - Housing (Box 131)
      - Museums (Box 131)
      - Schools (Box 131)
    - Sandown, NH (Box 131)
    - San Felipe, NM (Box 131)
    - San Fernando, CA (Box 131)
    - San Francisco, CA (Box 131)
      - Various (Box 131)
      - Planning (Box 131–132)
      - Bridges (Box 132)
        - Oakland Bay Bridge (Box 132)
        - Golden Gate Bridge (Box 132)
      - Churches (Box 132)
      - Clubs (Box 132)
        - Forest Hills Club (Box 132)
        - Pepsi Cola Center (Box 132)
      - Expositions (Box 132)
        - Golden Gate Exposition, 1939 (Box 132)
        - Panama-Pacific Exposition, 1915 (Box 132)
          - Court of Abundance (Box 132)
          - Court of Flowers (Box 132)
          - Court of the Four Seasons (Box 132)
          - Court of the Palms (Box 132)
          - Court of the Universe (Box 132)
          - Educational Building (Box 132)
          - Horticultural Universe (Box 132)
          - Machinery Building (Box 132)
          - Palace of the Fine Arts (Box 132)
          - Tower of Jewels (Box 132)
      - Government Buildings (Box 132)
        - City Hall (Box 132)
        - Civic Center (Box 133)
        - Court House (Box 133)
      - Hospitals (Box 133)
        - Maimonides Health Center (Box 133)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 133)
        - Various (Box 133)
        - Grover House (Box 133)
        - Kahn House (Box 133)
        - Loeb House (Box 133)
        - Morris House (Box 133)